It's been a while without your face
But I saw your picture on the wall the other day
Too much distance, too much space
You need to come back home and run along
I'm waiting for the light to change
You ask me how I've been and I'm good, I can't complain
Times get harder, things get strange
All I know, I don't want you gone
I know it hasn't been easy lately
But you don't want to leave me, baby
And you know I hate to keep you waiting
But when it's right, girl, it's right
Days turn into nights
Conversations turn into fights, we gon' be alright
Love turn into life
Girl, you been burnin' so bright, let me turn off the lights
Stay awake 'til the morning
It ain't always great, but it's never boring
And I been itching for your love
Don't want to feel a single thing if it ain't your touch
I get drunk and become numb
Just want to stumble into us
But baby, don't stop now 'cause it ain't over
Three years ago I was so dumb
Clueless, young and stupid, but look at who I have become
I ain't gonna break your heart, promise it's always safe
Baby, don't go now, pull me closer
I know it hasn't been easy lately
But you don't want to leave me, baby
You know I hate to keep you waiting
But I know when it's right, girl, it's right
Days turn into nights
Conversations turn into fights, we gon' be alright
'Cause love turn into life
Girl, you been burnin' so bright, let me turn off the lights
Stay awake 'til the morning
It ain't always great, but it's never boring
But when it's right, girl, it's right
There's a room somewhere up above the tree
And once you get there, you don't ever wanna leave no-no-no
Feelin' good, feelin' free
When I can finally get away
I need to see it with my own eyes
Hope it remembers that it knows my face
I'll come and see you if you don't mind
When I can finally get away
There's a place right up above the clouds
Somewhere in between later and right now
And you don't have to be scared, no
I'll be there
When I can finally get away
Soarin' uncontrollably
Gravity ain't holdin' me down
I'll fly to your front door some time
When I can finally get away